{
    "subject": "Camille_Keaton",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Meir_Zarchi",
    "human_readable": "Camille Keaton is married to Meir Zarchi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9478011727333069,
            "question": "Name the person Camille Keaton is married to."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9286351203918457,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Camille Keaton and Meir Zarchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9084739685058594,
            "question": "Who is Camille Keaton married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9046519994735718,
            "question": "Is Meir Zarchi married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843703866004944,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Camille Keaton and Meir Zarchi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203633427619934,
            "question": "To whom is Camille Keaton wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145437240600586,
            "question": "Who is Camille Keaton's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6980932950973511,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Camille Keaton's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6652638912200928,
            "question": "Who shares a marital relationship with Camille Keaton?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44195321202278137,
            "question": "What is Meir Zarchi known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Camille Keaton is married to Meir Zarchi.",
            "html": "yago_30269_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who shares a marital relationship with Camille Keaton?",
            "html": "yago_30269_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Camille Keaton's husband?",
            "html": "yago_30269_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Camille Keaton's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30269_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30269_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Camille Keaton was previously married to Meir Zarchi but that they divorced in 1982. There is no information suggesting she is currently married to him."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}